噢 跳得真美
Oh, that's beautiful.
糟透了 我做不到
It was terrible. I can't do it.
嗯 还没办法
Hmm, not yet.
但你以后会的
But you will.
你长得好快
You're growing up so fast.
你每次都这么说
You say that all the time.
是啊 因为你真的长很快
Yeah, it's because you are.
你长得真的好像你的姐姐
You look so much like your sister.
真希望我还记得她
I wish I could remember her.
要是我回来的时候 你又长高了一大截
If I come back and you're a foot taller...
我就要罚你禁足
gonna ground you.
嘘
Shh.
记得我们学过的 好吗
Remember what we learned, okay?
伊芙 跟我来
Eve, come with me.
保持安静
Stay quiet.
我们曾对你敞开心房
We opened our hearts to you.
我们接纳了你
We embraced you.
我们让你这个外人
We let you, an outsider
娶了我们家族的女儿
marry a daughter of our clan.
而你是怎么回报 这份好意的
And how did you repay this kindness?
你拿走了 根本不属于你的东西
You took what was not rightfully yours.
现在 你的妻子死了
And now, your wife is dead
为你的过错赎罪
to atone for your transgressions.
你以为你能够 就这样一走了之吗
Did you think that you could just walk away?
嗯
Hmm?
她在哪
Where is she?
伊芙在哪里
Where is Eve?
真迷人
Charming.
你这个他妈的胆小鬼
You're a fucking coward.
你只是想说服自己
You're trying to convince yourself
以为命运能让你 免于为自己的行为负责
that fate absolves you of your actions.
-这不是选择 -是啊
-There are no choices. -Yeah.
这样就能让你 比较好过吗
Does that make what you do any easier?
这让我做的事
It makes what I do...
成为必要
necessary.
一颗子弹
One bullet...
只要用对地方
well placed...
就能产生神奇的魔力
can be a magical thing.
它本身没有好坏
It's neither good...
也无关善恶
nor evil.
但一个人如何使用它
But how a man uses it
将会揭露他真实的本性
reveals his true character.
你想要有选择
You wanted choices.
好 选择来了
Well, here they are.
你自杀
You kill yourself,
你的女儿就能活下去
and your daughter lives.
或者杀了我
Or kill me
然后你跟你女儿 一起共赴黄泉
and you and your daughter die together.
由你选择
Choice is yours.
你已经有选择了
You've got your choice.
现在 你有种动手吗
Now, do you have the balls to do it?
爸爸
Papa!
嘿 宝贝 看着我
Hey, baby, look at me.
没事的
It's okay.
来吧
Come on.
爸爸
Papa.
对不起 宝贝
I'm sorry, honey.
-我从不希望你经历这些 -爸爸
-I never wanted this for you. -Papa.
对不起
I'm sorry.
爸爸
Papa!
Papa...
柴可夫斯基 真动听
Tchaikovsky. How lovely.
在痛失亲人时
At a time of loss
同情是最简单的
there's nothing easier than pity
而真相是最难面对的
and nothing more difficult than the truth,
因为悲伤从来没有简单的解答
as there are no easy answers for grief.
我想跟你说实话
I'd like to be honest with you.
可以吗
Would that be all right?
你父亲是个好人
Your father was a good man.
他希望你能拥有一个 自由开放的人生
He wanted a free and open life for you.
而不是像他那样 必须忍受煎熬
Not like the one that he had to endure.
但我们都得为 自己做的决定负责
But we all live with the decisions we make.
现在他离开你了
Now he's been taken from you.
对此我无能为力
I can do nothing about that.
但我能做的是
But what I can do...
带你去找他的家人
is offer to take you to his family.
他们会照顾你
They will look after you
而且 希望
and, hopefully...
有一天 他们也能成为你的家人
one day become your family, too.
总监现在要见你
The Director will see you now.
她知道她父母的真实身分吗
Does she know who her parents really were?
过来 坐
Come here. Sit.
你会跳舞 对吧
You dance, yes?
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm.
我经营这间剧院
I run this theater
而且我总是在寻找新血
and I am always looking for new recruits.
我了解你
I know you.
我了解你的痛苦
I know your pain.
也了解你内心深处 那股翻腾的情绪
What boils inside of you under the surface.
我可以给你一个 宣泄愤怒的地方
I can give you somewhere to put that anger.
那些人夺走了你的过去
Those men took your past.
别让他们 再偷走你的未来
Don't let them steal your future.
怎么样
Well?
她说我今后的路 就在这里
She says my path is now here
跟罗斯卡罗马在一起
with the Ruska Roma.
很好
Very well...
伊芙
Eve.
谢谢你 温斯顿先生
Thank you, Mr. Winston.
别客气 玛卡罗小姐
You are most welcome, Miss MaCarro.
要知道 我永远为您效劳
And know that I will always be at your service.
我叫诺吉
My name is Nogi.
你认识我父亲吗
Did you know my father?
我认识
I did.
你父亲是罗斯卡罗马 跟我一样
Your father was Ruska Roma, like me.
你以后也会是
Like you will be, too.
他是我们所说的「奇奇莫拉」
He was what we call Kikimora.
那是什么
What is that?
在斯拉夫神话里
In Slavic mythology
奇奇莫拉是一种鬼怪
the Kikimora is a kind of spirit
专门对付那些内心黑暗的人
to those with darkness in their hearts.
她可以充满报复心 且具毁灭性
She can be vengeful and destructive.
就像床边的鬼怪
Like the boogeyman?
是的
Yes.
但对于无辜的人
But to the innocent...
她可以是个守护者
she can be a protector.
这就
It is...
像是一体
two sides...
的两面
to the one coin.
去杀戮
To kill...
去拯救
To save.
但 终究
But, ultimately...
要由你自己来选择
it is up to you to choose.
十二年后
再来
你结束了吗
Are you finished?
还没
No.
很好
Good.
今天就到此为止
That will be all for today.
处理一下你的伤口 免得败血症
Tend to your wounds before you get sepsis
到时候我们得把你的脚砍掉
and we have to cut off your feet.
跟塔提安娜说 下一个到她
Tell Tatiana she's next.
「女王陛下」说轮到你了
"Her Majesty" says you're up.
那个女人讨厌我
That woman hates me.
她讨厌每一个人
She hates everybody.
老天 伊芙
Christ, Eve.
你为什么要这样 把自己逼这么紧
Why do you push yourself like this?
我想做好准备
I want to be ready.
准备什么
Ready for what?
你知道好笑的是什么吗
You know what's funny?
我小时候
When I was a little girl
还真的想当个 真正的芭蕾舞者
I actually did want to be a real ballerina.
你就是个真正的芭蕾舞者
You are a real ballerina.
你是这里跳得最好的
You're the best dancer here.
至于其他的破事 训练一下就学会了
That other shit, you'll learn with training.
开火
Fire!
一颗子弹
One bullet
只要用对地方
well placed
就能改变世界
can change the world.
而奇奇莫拉的使命 就是挡下那颗子弹
The Kikimora's purpose is to stop that bullet.
时间到
Time's up!
要成为奇奇莫拉 你必须先成为刺客
To become Kikimora you must become the assassin.
你必须学会像他一样行动
You must learn to move like him
像他一样思考
and think like him.
接下来的练习
For this next exercise
我们会使用模拟弹
we will be using simulated rounds.
规则是什么
What are the rules?
不计一切代价保护你的目标
Protect your ward at all costs.
这是唯一的规则
That is the only rule.
你为什么会失败
Why did you fail?
他太强壮了
He's too strong.
你真的以为
Do you really believe
力量跟输赢
that strength has anything to do
有任何关系吗
with whether you win or lose?
你永远都会比较弱小
You will always be weaker.
你永远都会比较娇小 而且处于劣势
You will always be smaller and at a disadvantage.
他之所以能打赢你
He is beating you
是因为你让他
because you are allowing him
来决定这场比赛的规则
to define the terms of the contest.
你想赢吗
You want to win?
那就改变规则
Change the terms.
随机应变 适应 耍点手段
Improvise, adapt, cheat.
善用你的强项
Lean into your strengths
而不是他的
not his.
用女孩子的方式去打
Fight like a girl.
开始
Begin.
很好
Good.
她在哪
Where is she?
塔提安娜的东西不见了 她出什么事了吗
Tatiana's things are gone. Did something happen to her?
坐下
Sit.
塔提安娜不具备 继续留在罗斯卡罗马
Tatiana did not have the qualities required
所需要的特质
to continue with the Ruska Roma.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
她缺乏我在你身上看到的 那种杀手本能
She lacked the killer instinct I see in you.
你的童年被夺走了
Your childhood was taken.
这份痛苦是你的动力
This pain is what drives you.
而塔提安娜
Tatiana...
她有的是悲伤 而不是痛苦
there is sadness, not pain.
这是有区别的
There's a difference.
你们俩现在走上 不同的道路了
You two are now on different paths.
那你为什么要一直压着我
Then why are you holding me back?
我准备好了
I'm ready.
或许你说得对
Perhaps you are right.
是时候了
It is time.
这是你训练的 最后一个阶段
This is the final stage of your training.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你他妈的在跟我开玩笑吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
我他妈的只是一个测验
I'm a fucking test?
真是虎落平阳被犬欺啊
How the mighty have fallen.
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
不知道
No.
我就是你
I'm you...
在十年后的你 真他妈的惨
in ten fucking years.
你好不容易逃出去了
Somehow you managed to get out
结果现在又回到原点
but here you are back where you began.
这一切到底是为了什么
All of this for what?
就因为一只小狗
那可不是 普通小狗
有了这个 乔达尼
With this, Jardani
你的票券就被撕毁了
your ticket is torn.
你永远都回不了家了
You can never come home again.
带他去救生船
Take him to the lifeboat.
再会了
Do svidanya.
再会
Das vedanya.
你就是他
You're him.
他们称之为「杀神」的那个人
The one they call the Baba Yaga.
学生们都在谈论你
The students all talk about you.
我要怎么离开这里
How do I get outta here?
前门没锁
The front door is unlocked.
不 我的意思是
No. I mean...
我要怎么开始 做你做的那种事
how do I start doing what you do?
看来你已经开始了
Looks like you already have.
那扇门会比你想像中 更快地锁上
That door will lock sooner than you think.
你还可以离开
You can still leave.
你还有选择
You still have a choice.
你为什么不离开
Why didn't you leave?
我正在想办法
I'm working on it.
总监觉得你准备好了
The Director feels you are ready
可以接第一份合约了
for your first contract.
你要保护这个女人
You will protect this woman.
凯特拉·帕克
Katla Park.
她父亲是我们的主要客户
Her father is our primary charge.
他担心他的竞争对手
He is concerned that his competitors
会试图绑架他女儿来威胁他
may try to get to him by ransoming his daughter.
你的工作就是确保 他们没有机会得逞
Your job is to make sure they don't get the chance.
为了渗透安保系统
To infiltrate past security
你要用这把改造过的 3D打印的克拉克43X
you'll be using a modified 3D printed Glock 43X
配有强化碳纤维枪管
with reinforced carbon fiber barrel
和塑胶子弹
and polymer rounds.
橡胶子弹
Rubber bullets?
有问题吗
Problem?
-没有 -你会在「负十一」夜店
-No. -You'll find Miss Park
找到帕克小姐
at Minus Eleven.
已就位
In position.
收到
Copy.
目标已进入视线
I have the principal in sight.
保持位置
Hold your position.
她舞跳得不错
She can dance.
十点钟方向有动静
I got movement at ten o'clock.
是威胁吗
A threat?
待命
Stand by.
嘿
Hey!
绝对是威胁
Definitely a threat.
你应该让开
You should get out of the way.
我不能
I can't.
我懂
I understand.
嘿
Hey!
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我现在不想让任何人碰我
I don't want anyone to touch me right now.
嘿 嘿没事的
Hey, hey. It's okay.
你现在安全了 没事了
You're safe now, it's fine.
我们带你离开这里
Let's get you out of here.
两个月后
嘿 上面到底 他妈的发生什么事了
Hey, what the hell is goin' on up there?
有没有人回应
Somebody respond.
你被困在电梯里了吗
Were you stuck in the elevator?
对超可怕的
Yes. It was very scary.
小姐 你的袋子 好像有东西漏出来
Miss, something's leaking from your bag.
是啊 谢谢你
Yes. Thank you.
不客气
No problem.
你带一只断手来找我 是有什么原因吗
Is there a reason you've brought me a severed hand?
你看这道疤
Look at the scar.
我以前见过这个
I've seen this before.
这道疤痕跟
That's the same scar
那个杀了我父亲的男人一样
as the man who murdered my father.
那是一个部落的印记
It was a mark from a tribe.
你早就知道他们是谁了
You knew who they were.
你好大的胆子
How dare you?
我一直都在保护你
I have been protecting you.
你为什么不告诉我他们是谁
Why didn't you tell me who they were?
我的孩子 你不明白
My child, you do not understand.
有那种印记的人
People with that mark
他们没有规矩 不计后果 也毫无怜悯之心
they have no rules, no consequence, no mercy.
他们不干涉我们的生意
They do not interfere with our business
我们也不干涉他们的
and we do not interfere with theirs.
这个协定跟罗斯卡罗马 本身一样古老
This is a pact as old as the Ruska Roma itself.
这些规矩 到底是在保护谁
All these rules, who are they serving?
当你做的生意是见血的
When you deal in blood
就必须有规矩
there must be rules...
否则谁都活不下去
or nothing survives.
一个部落为什么要试图绑架小孩
Why would a tribe try to kidnap a child?
我警告你
I am warning you
你是找不到他们的
you will not find them
而追查他们只会带来混乱
and hunting for them will only bring chaos.
我命令你
I'm ordering you
不准追查这件事
do not pursue this.
我说得够清楚了吗
Do I make myself clear?
遵命 总监教母
麻烦
Please...
把你的手拿走
take your hand.
欢迎来到大陆饭店
Welcome to the Continental.
要入住吗
Checking in?
不 我想跟经理谈谈
No. I'd like to speak with the manager.
他有跟您约好吗
Is he expecting you?
不 他没有
No, he's not.
我明白了
I see.
请问 您的姓名是
And what, may I ask, is your name?
伊芙
Eve.
伊芙·玛卡罗
Eve MaCarro.
我看看我能做些什么
Let me see what I can do.
罗斯卡罗马的伊芙·玛卡罗
Eve MaCarro of the Ruska Roma.
真高兴再次见到你
What a pleasure to see you again.
请
Please.
那么 是什么风把你吹来的
So, what brings you here?
我在找杀害我父亲的那个部落
I'm looking for the tribe that killed my father.
如果我建议你不要这么做呢
And if I suggested you didn't?
我会微笑点头 然后当没听到
I would smile and nod and then ignore you.
啊
Ah.
总监已经警告过我 关于他们的事
The Director has already warned me about them
还有那些规矩
and the rules.
所以我能理解你的顾虑
So, I can appreciate your reluctance.
你这么说真是太客气了
That's very kind of you
但容我给你几句忠告 玛卡罗小姐
but a few words of advice, if I may, Miss MaCarro.
无论你觉得这些人身上有什么情报
Whatever information you think these people have
知道了可能对你没有好处
it might not be in your best interests to know it.
我还是需要知道
I still need to know.
「需要知道」这四个字 就是当年害我们
"Needing to know" is what got us banished
被逐出伊甸园的原因
from the Garden of Eden.
你准备好再次被逐出去了吗 伊芙
Are you prepared to be cast out again, Eve?
拜讬了
Please.
好吧
Very well.
我告诉你这个那不是部落 是一个邪教
I'll give you this. It's not a tribe, it's a cult.
他们杀人不仅是为了生意
That kills not just for business
也是为了寻乐
but for sport.
我们生活在所谓的文明社会里
While we live among so-called polite society
但他们不是
they do not.
我在哪里可以找到他们
Where can I find them?
确切地点不明
The precise location is unknown.
但他们入住我们饭店时 我们会监控他们
But we do monitor them when they stay at our hotels.
他们可以住进大陆饭店
They have access to the Continentals?
哦 是的 与其让他们在外面对着帐篷撒尿
Oh yes. Better to have them inside the tent, pissing out
还不如让他们在帐篷里往外尿
than outside, pissing in.
而且没错 现在有个身上有那印记的男人
And, yes, there is a man who bears that mark
正住在我们其中一间饭店
staying at one of our hotels at the present...
我想是在布拉格
in Prague, I believe.
为了什么生意
On what business?
我们继续
Shall we?
哈啰 亲爱的
Hello, my dear.
穆丽尔 麻烦你一下
Muriel, be a darling
把「黑网」上关于 丹尼尔·派恩的
and bring up the latest Blackwire submissions
最新提交内容叫出来
on a Daniel Pine.
丹尼尔·派恩
Daniel Pine...
合约三天前提交
Contract submitted three days ago.
他的悬赏金额是两百万
His bounty is set at two million.
他目前躲在 布拉格大陆饭店
He's currently holed up inside the Prague Continental...
315号房
room 3-1-5.
没有任何外线电话记录
No outside calls have been logged
但他点了一大堆的客房服务
and he's purchased a shitload of room service.
大部分是冰淇淋
Mostly ice cream.
爱吃甜食 嗯
Sweet tooth, hmm?
请给我纸本
Hard copy, please.
先生
Sir...
有您的电话
there is a call for you.
是总监打来的
From The Director.
祝你好运 女士
办理入住
Checking in.
当然
Certainly.
请问您打算住多久
And how long will you be staying with us?
只住一晚
Just the night.
麻烦给我314号房
Room 314, please.
派恩还是没有动静
Still no movement from Pine.
我的命令是什么
What are my orders?
盯紧派恩
Keep your eyes on Pine.
可能有人要接单了
We may have a taker.
你说对了
You're right.
有人接单了
We have a taker.
一个女人 年轻 黑发
A woman, young, dark hair.
她进去了
She's in.
你是谁
Who are you?
妈的
Shit.
你不该说那个字的
You're not supposed to say that word.
对 抱歉
Right. Sorry.
-你叫什么名字？ -艾拉
-What's your name? -Ella.
我是伊芙
I'm Eve.
你不是来伤害我爸的吧
You're not here to hurt my daddy, are you?
你父亲
Your father?
艾拉 过来这里
Ella, come here.
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be all right.
你要不要站到我后面来 甜心
Why don't you come stand behind me, sweetheart?
你想要什么
What do you want?
我小时候
When I was a child
一群有你那种印记的人 杀了我父亲
men with your mark murdered my father.
我只想知道去哪里可以找到他们
I just want to know where to find them.
你完全不知道你刚趟进什么浑水里了 对吧
You have no idea what you just walked into, do you?
没有进行任何业务
No business being conducted.
他们只是在聊天
They're just talking.
合约服务部
Contract services.
有什么能为您服务
How can I help you?
帐户8-6-5-1
Account 8-6-5-1.
合约上的姓名
Name on contract?
丹尼尔·派恩
Daniel Pine.
将合约金额加倍
Double the contract.
艹
Fuck.
你刚刚把所有事情 都搞得更糟了
You just made everything a whole lot worse.
你在找的那些人
Those people that you're looking for?
他们现在正包围着这家饭店
They're surrounding this hotel right now
就等着有人破坏规矩 上钩
hoping somebody breaks the rules and takes the bait.
我想他们就是希望 上钩的那个人是你
I think they were hoping that somebody was gonna be you.
现在 你害他们坐不住了
Now, you've just made 'em antsy.
他们为什么会在这家饭店
Why would they be at the hotel?
他们只是想杀了我 好抓到她
They just want me dead to get to her.
宝贝 趴下
Baby, stay down!
艾拉 快点
Ella, come on.
快点
Come on.
他在移动在走廊
He's moving. Hallway.
该死
Damn it!
快走
Come on.
退后 退后 退后 走另一边走
Back, back, back the other way. Go!
等等 等等躲到我后面
Wait, wait. Get behind me.
快点
Come on.
艾拉 甜心
Ella, honey...
我们走
let's go.
他们为什么想要她
Why do they want her?
这是个邪教
It's a cult.
没人能脱身
No one gets out.
永远
Ever.
你得帮我 把艾拉带离这里
You gotta help me get Ella outta here.
她值得过比这更好的生活
She deserves a better life than this.
我不能 我来这里不是为了这个
I can't. That's not why I'm here.
你是奇奇莫拉
You're Kikimora.
那不就是你做的事吗
Isn't that what you do?
帮我保护她
Help me protect her.
我就告诉你去哪里找到他们
I'll tell you where to find them.
拜讬你
Please?
爸爸
Daddy...
我们会死吗
are we going to die?
不会
No.
不会的 宝贝
No, baby.
不会的 今天不会
No, not today.
你可以相信她
You can trust her.
-嗨 -嗯
-Hi. -Huh?
没事了
It's okay.
-嘿 -还剩几个
-Hey. -How many left?
两个 也许十个
Two. Maybe ten.
哦 管他的
Oh, fuck it.
爸爸
Daddy!
喂
Yes?
我们抓到那女孩了
We have the girl.
很好
Good.
长官 那里还有另外一个人
Sir, there was someone else there.
谁
Who?
一个女人
A woman.
是为了合约来的吗
For the contract?
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
我想她可能是冲着艾拉来的
I think she might have been after Ella.
真的吗
Really?
我们 呃
Do we, uh...
我们知道她是谁吗
Do we know who she is?
还不知道
Not yet.
我把她留给大陆饭店的安保人员了
I left her for Continental security.
是他们先开始的
They started this.
那都是屁话
That's bullshit.
我没有违反任何规定
I did not break any rules.
-你打断了我他妈的下巴 -你还不是在用它
-You broke my fuckin' jaw. -You're still using it.
我没有杀任何人
I didn't kill anyone.
你需要办理退房了
You're going to need to check out.
了解
Understood.
今天想要点什么 女士
And what will it be today, madam?
我想去打猎
I'd like to go hunting.
你跟这些人做过生意吗
Have you ever done business with these people?
我没有
I have not.
但你听说过他们
But you know of them.
你知道的比我多 我跟你保证
You know more than me, I assure you.
我可以「坦白」说吗
May I be "frank"?
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm.
我比较喜欢保持现状
I prefer to keep it that way.
嗯
Hmm.
我们今天只是纯逛逛
Are we just window shopping today
还是你想买点什么
or would you like to make a purchase?
要看是什么货色
Depends on the merchandise.
您先请 女士
After you, madam.
借过一下
Pardon me.
那么
So...
这次是大型还是小型狩猎
will this be a large or small game hunt?
大型的
Large.
V7 先驱者TTI
The V Seven Harbinger TTI.
三十发.308口径子弹
Thirty rounds of .308.
上面有Trijicon AccuPoint 1-6倍 可变倍率瞄准镜
It's got a Trijicon AccuPoint 1-to-6 optical on top
万一你想近身来场 既分高下也决生死的私人决斗
and in case you wanna get up close and make it personal
侧面还配有RMR瞄准镜 专门应对这种快节奏缠斗
you've got a side RMR for the faster, dirtier stuff.
TTI订制 贝内利M2 21英寸鳍状握把
TTI custom Benelli M2 21-inch fin grip.
超大拉机柄 超大枪机释放钮
Oversized charging handle, oversized bolt release.
这能把熊头打爆
This will take a bear's head off.
轻轻松松
Easily.
噢 这是我个人的最爱
Oh, this is a personal favorite of mine.
这个
This...
啊！艹
Ah! Fuck!
混蛋！艹
Bastards! Fuck!
王八蛋
Motherfuckers.
好吧
All right...
你别透露是从我这打听到的
you didn't hear this from me.
他们的确切位置 从未被证实
Their precise location has never been confirmed
因为所有去找过的人
since anyone who's ever gone looking
也全都失踪了
has also gone missing.
这概率可不妙
That's bad math.
然而
However
有传言说 他们会聚集在这些山峰处
whispers suggest they've been known to gather
的某个地方
somewhere in these peaks
在亚伯西和费尔德基希过去 的山脉深处
deep in the mountains past Abersee and Feldkirk.
这线索不多
It's not much.
比我目前掌握的都多了
It's more than I had.
谢谢你
Thank you.
很抱歉你的店被砸了
Sorry about your shop.
我需要一辆车
I need a car.
你以为我不会发现吗
Did you think I would not find out?
你竟然公然违抗我的命令
That you expressly disobeyed my orders?
那你就告诉我他们是谁
Then tell me who they are.
我告诉过你 我们不跟他们往来
I told you, we do not engage with them.
你冒着毁掉我们家族的风险 就为了什么
You risk the destruction of our family, and for what?
你自己自私的理由
Your own selfish reasons.
立刻回来 否则我别无选择
Return at once or I will have no choice.
需要点什么吗
Can I get you anything?
一杯咖啡就好
Just a coffee.
来 我们走
Come, let's go.
是阿格妮莎
It's Agnetha!
派人去餐厅
Send somebody to the restaurant!
快
Hurry!
去绕到后面
Go around the back.
别让她跑了
Don't let her escape!
我不会伤害你
I'm not gonna hurt you.
搞什么
The fuck?
校长 这里是天眼
Chancellor, this is The Eye.
什么事
What is it?
那个外来者还没被控制住
The outsider has not been contained.
启动全部应对程序
Engage full protocols.
回室内小朋友们 快
找到她
Find her!
啊
Ah.
你们在开小茶会啊
You're having a little tea party.
你不跟你外公打声招呼吗
Aren't you going to say hello to your grandfather?
爸爸在哪
Where is Daddy?
他还好吗
Is he okay?
你不知道 艾拉 我有多担心
You have no idea, Ella, how worried I was.
我们所有人都很担心
All of us.
你爸爸
Your father...
嗯 他破坏了我们的习俗
well, he broke our customs.
他试图把你带走
He was trying to take you away.
带离我身边
Away from me.
带离你的家人身边
Away from your family.
我恨你
I hate you.
那份恨会让你变强 艾拉
That hate will make you strong, Ella.
我恨你
I hate you.
校长
Chancellor.
我们抓到她了
We got her.
她死了吗
Is she dead?
她是罗斯卡罗马
She's Ruska Roma.
她身上有他们的印记
She has their mark.
你知道吗 我见过 你们的总监一次
You know, I met your Director once.
是很多年前在莫斯科
It was many years ago in Moscow.
不是个很好相处的女士
Not a very pleasant lady.
但尽管如此 我们还是进行了一场互相尊重的对话
But we did have a respectful conversation, nonetheless.
我们都理解彼此扮演的角色
A shared understanding of the roles that we both play...
而且 更重要的是 我们不扮演的角色
and, more importantly, the roles that we don't play.
总监没有派我来
The Director didn't send me here.
罗斯卡罗马跟这件事无关
The Ruska Roma has nothing to do with this.
哦 但现在有关了
Well, it does now.
你为什么在这里
Why are you here?
如果你是为那女孩来的 你就大错特错了
If you've come for the girl, you are gravely mistaken.
艾拉是我的孙女
Ella is my granddaughter.
有一天 这一切都会是她的
Someday, all of this will be hers.
我儿子
My son
嗯
well...
他试图剥夺她 真正的血统传承
he tried to deprive her of her true heritage.
你对自己的儿子下悬赏令
You put a contract on your own son?
你可能注意到了 我们不太喜欢
You may have noticed we don't take well
外人干涉我们镇上的事
to outsiders meddling in our town.
这里都是像你这样的人 到此安家
This is where people like yourself come to live
过着真正的生活
to have real lives.
养育家庭
To raise families.
难道你不想有一天
Would you not like to someday
拥有自己的家庭吗
have a family of your own?
我曾经有过家庭
I had a family!
我那时还是个孩子
I was a child.
一群人闯进我家 一群来自你们部落的人
Men came into my house. Men from your tribe.
啊
Ah.
我明白了
I see.
这是为了复仇
This is about vengeance.
他们杀了我父亲
They killed my father
还想带走我
and tried to take me.
想带走你
Tried to take you?
命运真是件让人敬畏的事
Fate is a very humbling thing.
怎么了
What is it?
嗯 她...她不是为派恩工作的
Well, she... she wasn't working for Pine.
她会在这里 是因为我杀了她父亲
She's here because I killed her father
在她还是个孩子的时候
when she was a child.
她是你妹妹
She's your sister.
不
No.
看在老天的份上
For God's sake!
你在做什么
What are you doing?
莉娜
Lena!
这么多年来 我一直以为你死了
All this time, I thought you were dead.
你在说什么
What are you talkin' about?
你不记得我了 对吗
You don't remember me, do you?
你是在这里出生的 伊芙
You were born here, Eve.
我们都是
We both were.
我的小妹妹回家了
My little sister has come home.
我小时候 常常在想
When I was younger, I used to wonder...
「为什么他带走你 而不是我？」
"Why did he take you and not me?"
我是说 后来我才意识到 对我来说已经太晚了
I mean, later I realized it was too late for me.
我已经杀过人了
I'd already taken a life.
但是你
But you...
他以为他可以把你养大
He thought he could raise you
让你对这个地方毫无记忆
with no memory of this place
对你真正的家毫无记忆
of your true home.
但我猜那东西已经融入你的血里 对吧
But I guess it never leaves your blood, does it?
到头来
In the end
我们就是我们
we are who we are.
我们不一样
We are not the same.
你的人
Your people...
杀了我父亲
killed my father.
是我们的父亲 没错
Our father. Yes.
因为他背叛了我们
For betraying us.
然后我们的母亲 不得不付出代价
And then our mother had to pay the price.
那天晚上校长是想救你
The Chancellor was trying to save you that night.
他试着把你带回家
He was trying to bring you back home
就像他对待任何人一样
as he would with anyone.
我父亲是想给我一个正常的生活
My father was trying to give me a normal life!
嗯 他会很骄傲的
Well, he would be very proud.
你在强迫孩子们过这种生活
You're forcing children into this life!
就像罗斯卡罗马对你做的一样
As Ruska Roma has with you.
不
No!
她给了我一个选择！这是我选的
She gave me a choice! I chose this!
哦 是吗
Oh, did you?
还是命运只是为你 找到了另一条路
Or did fate just find another path for you?
至少在这里 我们对自己很诚实
At least here we're honest about who we are.
没有奇奇莫拉的谎言
No Kikimora lies.
我们看到她了
We've got eyes on her.
83号小屋
Cabin 83.
长官 她和莉娜在里面 在说话
She's inside with Lena, sir, talking.
干掉他们
Take them out.
长官
Sir?
两个都杀了
Kill them both.
你听到校长说的了 炸掉它
You heard The Chancellor. Blow it.
我才九岁 他们就告诉我们你死了
I was only nine when they told us you were dead.
省省力气吧
Save your breath.
我想你
I missed you.
所有人 行动
Everyone, move in.
检查有没有生还者
Check for survivors.
突击队
Strike team...
突击队 收到吗
Strike team, do you copy?
解决了吗
Is it done?
这件事要等你死了才算结束
This isn't done until you're dead.
喂
Yes?
你我之间有个问题
We have a problem, you and I.
那会是什么问题呢
And what problem might that be?
你部落的一名成员
That a member of your tribe
违反了长达数世纪的休战协议
has contravened a centuries old truce.
罗斯卡罗马不想开战
The Ruska Roma have no desire for a war.
尤其是不想跟你开战
Especially not with you.
不管是不是你派她来的
Whether you sent her or not
我都不感兴趣
is of no interest to me.
你将承担她行为的
You will accept full consequences
所有后果
of her actions.
也就是
Which are?
你部落的末日
The end of your tribe.
你的学生 你他妈的宠物 所有的一切
Your students, your fucking pets, everything.
把她叫回来
Call her off.
校长 她是在违背
Chancellor, she's operating
罗斯卡罗马的意愿下行动的
against Ruska Roma.
就算我想 也叫不回她
I could not call her off if I tried.
那战争就势在必行了
Then war it shall be
或许我们可以达成一个协议
Perhaps an agreement could be struck.
我可以派人去解决这个问题
I can send someone to solve the problem.
一个有能力的人
Someone capable.
不再有流血事件
No more bloodshed.
如果你同意
If you agree to this
你也必须同意你的人不会出手
you must also agree that your men will not engage.
如果午夜来临她还活着
If come midnight she still breathes
报复将会是无可避免且全面的
retaliation will be inevitable and total.
如果问题解决了呢
And if the problem is taken care of?
那我就会重新考虑我的回应
Then I will reconsider my response.
很好
Very well.
我当然需要你的位置
I will, of course, need your location.
我保证 这个秘密会跟我一起进棺材
A secret I assure you will die with me.
夫人 她是自己人
Madam, she is family.
她已经做出了选择
She has made her choice.
杀神
The Baba Yaga.
哈尔施塔特的居民们
Citizens of Hallstatt...
这道命令在钟声响起前持续有效
this order stays in effect until the bells ring out.
从现在起 你们不准交战
As of now, you do not engage.
任何胆敢违抗此令者
Anyone who feels compelled to go against this order
将被驱逐出境
will be cast out.
让狼去追捕它的猎物吧
Leave the wolf to its prey.
她派你来杀我
She sent you here to kill me?
那要看你自己
That's up to you.
或者你可以离开
Or you can leave.
由你选择
Your choice.
你还记得我吗
Do you remember me?
在剧院的时候
From the theater?
记得你对我说的话吗
Remember what you said to me?
你告诉我可以离开
You told me I could leave
那是我的选择
that it was my choice.
现在仍然是
It still is.
我不走
I'm not leaving.
你不必这么做
You don't have to do this.
快走
Just leave.
走
Leave.
快...走吧
Just... go.
他杀了我父亲
He killed my father.
我知道
I know.
让我了结这一切
Let me finish this.
晚上11:32
午夜前
Midnight.
如果还没解决
If it isn't done...
按规矩处置
Rules.
还有承担一切后果
And consequences.
长官 他放走了她 而且她正在攻击
Sir, he's let her go and she's on the attack.
我建议我们重新启动全部应对程序
I recommend we re-engage full protocols.
注意
Attention.
所有居民现在被号召 追捕外来者
Every citizen is now being called to hunt the outsider.
我们走
Let's go.
快点 快点
Let's move it, move it!
检查船库
Check the boathouse.
你看到什么了吗
You see anything?
她在这
She's here!
快点！跟我来
Hurry up! With me.
保持警惕
Be on alert.
确保所有区域都清空了
Make sure everything is clear.
此面向敌
酷
Cool.
注意
Attention.
外来者已进入军火库
The outsider has entered the armory.
所有队伍前往军火库
All teams proceed to the armory.
她想要我
She wants me...
而且她也想要艾拉
and she wants Ella.
命令
Orders?
你找到她
You find her...
然后毁了她
and you destroy her.
快点
Come on.
眼睛睁大点
Keep your eyes open.
军火库入口 有两个人倒下
Two men down at the armory entrance.
我重复 军火库入口 有两个人倒下
I repeat, two men down at the armory entrance.
守在那里 守住
Hold there. Hold.
上！上
Go! Go!
请求所有居民
Requesting all citizens
立刻前往隧道
to the tunnels immediately.
所有居民前往隧道
All citizens proceed to the tunnels.
进去 我掩护你
Move in. I got your six.
噢 糟了
Oh, shit.
在那里
Over there!
走 走
Go, go!
她在那
She's there!
我们跟丢了外来者
We have lost sight of the outsider.
所有队伍保持警惕
All teams be on alert.
继续巡逻周边
Continue to patrol the perimeter.
我们在广场天眼 回报 回报
We're on the square. Eye, report back. Report back.
我们在广场
We're on the square.
阿尔法小队 停
Alpha Team, halt!
她已经离开隧道了
She has exited the tunnels.
检查你后面
Check behind you.
长官
Sir.
为了哈尔施塔特的存续
In the interest of Hallstatt's survival
最好是将您转移
it would be best to relocate you.
两百年来 没有一位哈尔施塔特的领袖
In 200 years, no leader of Hallstatt
曾离开权力宝座
has ever left the seat of power
去寻求庇护
to seek shelter.
我明白
I understand.
但是 长官 我们也跟丢了约翰·威克
But, sir, we've also lost track of John Wick.
放手
Let go!
放开我
Let go of me.
晚上11:56
注意 请求所有居民
Attention. Requesting all citizens...
这是自杀 那可是他妈的约翰·威克
This is suicide. It's fucking John Wick.
来吧 他只有一个人
Come on. He's only one man.
从这里抄小路过去
Cut across here.
你不觉得我们已经闹够了吗
Don't you think we've had enough?
你真的以为你能从我手上 救走她吗
Do you really think you're going to save her from me?
从
From...
从这一切之中
From all of this?
不管这里发生什么
Whatever happens here...
什么都不会改变
nothing is going to change.
村庄会继续存在
The village will remain
孩子们会被抚养长大
the children will be raised
而这个体系会像过去
and the system will continue as it has
一千年一样继续运作
for the last thousand years.
看看你
Look at you.
你知道你不是选择成为杀手
You know that you don't choose to be a killer
你是被选中的
you are chosen.
就像你的姐姐被选中一样
Just like your sister was chosen.
就像艾拉被选中一样
Just like Ella has been chosen.
这是你的命运
It is your fate
你无法改变它
and you cannot change it.
你唯一在对抗的人是你自己
The only person you're fighting is yourself...
没事了
It's okay.
我们走
Let's go.
嗯
Hmm?
乔达尼
Jardani?
解决好了
所以 她死了
So, she is dead?
他死了
He is dead.
很好
Fine.
爸爸
Daddy?
嘿 甜心
Hey, sweetie.
过来
Come here.
上来这里
Get up here.
814号房
Room 814.
我相信谈得很顺利吧
I trust the talk went well?
要入住了 嗯
Checking in, hmm?
是的
Yes.
安全的避风港 玛卡罗小姐
Safe haven, Miss MaCarro.
你或许砍掉了蛇头
You may have cut the snake's head
但蛇身还活着
but the body still lives.
他们会来找你的
They'll be looking for you.
合约服务部 有什么能为您服务
Contract services. How may I help you?
帐户姓名是
Name on the account?
处理中
Processing.
「黑网」新合约 目标:伊芙·玛卡罗 $5,000,000
第2位:QU5洛克曼 第3位:BX1玛卡罗 第4位:MH7布鲁门伯格
♩ 再靠近一步 你就全是我的 ♩
♩ One step closer and you're all mine ♩
♩ 你让我别无选择 ♩
♩ You leave me no choice ♩
♩ 深深烙印在我脑海 ♩
♩ Burned into mind ♩
♩ 我将会给予致命一击 ♩
♩ I'm going in for the kill ♩
♩ 你已经无路可逃 ♩
♩ There is no other way out ♩
♩ 如果你需要的话 宝贝 ♩
♩ If you need to baby ♩
♩ 哭吧 尽情哭啊 你怎么不哭 ♩
♩ Cry, cry about it Why don't you cry ♩
♩ 为你开的头 付出代价吧 ♩
♩ Time to pay for what you started ♩
♩ 现在谁后悔了 ♩
♩ Who's sorry now ♩
♩ 继续说你的谎 尽管耍嘴皮子 ♩
♩ Tell your lies Yeah, you can run your mouth ♩
♩ 但你敢像个女孩一样战斗吗 ♩
♩ But can you fight like a girl ♩
♩ 像个女孩一样战斗 ♩
♩ Fight like a girl ♩
♩ 然后夺下这个世界 ♩
♩ And take this world ♩
♩ 今晚 你是受害者 ♩
♩ Tonight, you're the victim ♩
♩ 因你自己的罪行 ♩
♩ Of your own crime ♩
♩ 你做出了选择 ♩
♩ You made your choice ♩
♩ 你将吞下你的命运 ♩
♩ You'll swallow your fate ♩
♩ 冷若冰霜 ♩
♩ Stone cold ♩
♩ 喂养毒蛇 ♩
♩ Feed the snakes ♩
♩ 燃起那火焰 呼喊我的名字 ♩
♩ Hold that fire Say my name ♩
♩ 宝贝 你可以哭 ♩
♩ Baby, you can cry ♩
♩ 哭吧 尽情哭啊 ♩
♩ Cry, cry about it ♩
♩ 你怎么不哭 ♩
♩ Why don't you cry ♩
♩ 为你开的头 付出代价吧 ♩
♩ Time to pay for what you started ♩
♩ 现在谁后悔了 ♩
♩ Who's sorry now ♩
♩ 继续说你的谎 ♩
♩ Tell your lies ♩
♩ 是啊 你可以继续耍嘴皮子 ♩
♩ Yeah, you can run your mouth ♩
♩ 但你敢像个女孩一样战斗吗 ♩
♩ But can you fight like a girl ♩
♩ 像个女孩一样战斗 ♩
♩ Fight like a girl ♩
♩ 罪人与救世主 我游走在界线 ♩
♩ Sinner and savior I've been walking the line ♩
♩ 杀手们的对决 ♩
♩ Killers collide ♩
♩ 肾上腺素飙升的快感 ♩
♩ The feeling an adrenaline high ♩
♩ 暴力因子在我血液里流动 ♩
♩ Violent behavior in my blood ♩
♩ 除了自己无人可信 ♩
♩ No one but myself to trust ♩
♩ 复仇那玩意真是他妈的毒品 ♩
♩ Vengeance well that shit's a hell of a drug ♩
♩ 打破循环 我可不想 ♩
♩ Break the cycle I don't wanna ♩
♩ 折断你脊椎 我倒想这么干 ♩
♩ Break your spinal yeah I'm gonna ♩
♩ 我的手指在板机上 ♩
♩ My finger on the trigger ♩
♩ 我一直在滋养痛苦 ♩
♩ I've been feeding the pain ♩
♩ 你永远无法像女孩一样战斗 ♩
♩ You'll never fight like a girl ♩
♩ 所以我总能赢得这场游戏 ♩
♩ So I keep winning the game ♩
♩ 我想看你哭 ♩
♩ I wanna see you cry ♩
♩ 哭吧 尽情哭啊 ♩
♩ Cry, cry about it ♩
♩ 你怎么不哭 ♩
♩ Why don't you cry ♩
♩ 为你开的头 付出代价吧 ♩
♩ Time to pay for what you started ♩
♩ 现在谁后悔了 继续说你的谎 ♩
♩ Who's sorry now Tell your lies ♩
♩ 是啊 你可以继续耍嘴皮子 ♩
♩ Yeah, you can run your mouth ♩
♩ 但你敢像个女孩一样战斗吗 ♩
♩ But can you fight like a girl ♩
♩ 罪人与救世主 我游走在界线 ♩
♩ Sinner and savior I've been walking the line ♩
♩ 伪装的恶魔 ♩
♩ Devil disguised ♩
♩ 当我望向你双眼就看见了 ♩
♩ I see it when I look in your eyes ♩
♩ 是啊 你可以继续耍嘴皮子 ♩
♩ Yeah, you can run your mouth ♩
♩ 但你敢像个女孩一样战斗吗 ♩
♩ But can you fight like a girl ♩
♩ 像个女孩一样战斗 ♩
♩ Fight like a girl ♩
♩ 我知道我本该保有骄傲 ♩
♩ I know I should have the pride ♩
♩ 我知道我本该保有骨气 ♩
♩ I know I should have the spirit ♩
♩ 我知道你会撒谎 ♩
♩ I know you would tell a lie ♩
♩ 只要你以为我听不到 ♩
♩ If you knew I couldn't hear it ♩
♩ 你会说得 噢 如此骄傲 ♩
♩ You'd say it oh, so proudly ♩
♩ 但你可曾意识到自己的罪 ♩
♩ But do you know your crimes ♩
♩ 你可曾想起过我 ♩
♩ And do you think about me ♩
♩ 你又是否曾属于过我 ♩
♩ And were you ever mine ♩
♩ 你说我对你意义非凡 ♩
♩ You say I mean the world to you ♩
♩ 只是为了让我对你俯首称臣 ♩
♩ To keep me on my knees ♩
♩ 然后将刀子捅得更深 ♩
♩ Then dig the knife in deeper ♩
♩ 只为看着我血流不止 ♩
♩ Just to watch how much I bleed ♩
♩ 我被剥得体无完肤 我不想孤单一人 ♩
♩ I'm stripped to the bone I don't want to be alone ♩
♩ 无论我如何恳求 ♩
♩ No matter how I plead ♩
♩ 你这么做 只因你吃定了我 ♩
♩ You do it 'cause you know you can ♩
♩ 才转身反咬那喂养你的手 ♩
♩ Turn around and bite the hand that feeds ♩
♩ 你打破的每一个承诺 ♩
♩ Every promise that you break ♩
♩ 每一次你试图将错怪到我头上 ♩
♩ Every time you try to place the blame on me ♩
♩ 我不想再控制这份痛苦 ♩
♩ I don't want to control the pain ♩
♩ 将它化为我需要的火焰 ♩
♩ Turn it into the fire I need ♩
♩ 这感觉流遍我全身 ♩
♩ The feeling rushes through me ♩
♩ 你还能听见我的哭喊吗 ♩
♩ Can you still hear me cry ♩
♩ 但终究我还是站起来了 ♩
♩ But after all I'm standing ♩
♩ 这一次靠我自己 ♩
♩ On my own this time ♩
♩ 你说我对你意义非凡 ♩
♩ You say I mean the world to you ♩
♩ 只是为了让我跪下 让我跪下 ♩
♩ To keep me on my knees Keep me on my knees ♩
♩ 然后将刀子捅得更深 ♩
♩ Then dig the knife in deeper ♩
♩ 只为看着我血流不止 ♩
♩ Just to watch how much I bleed ♩
♩ 我被剥得体无完肤 我不想孤单一人 ♩
♩ I'm stripped to the bone I don't want to be alone ♩
♩ 无论我如何恳求 ♩
♩ No matter how I plead ♩
♩ 你这么做 只因你吃定了我 ♩
♩ You do it 'cause you know you can ♩
♩ 才转身反咬那喂养你的手 ♩
♩ Turn around and bite the hand that feeds ♩
♩ 我玩腻了你扭曲的游戏 扭曲的游戏 ♩
♩ I played your twisted game Played your twisted game ♩
♩ 现在看我浴火重生 ♩
♩ Now watch me walk through the flames ♩
♩ 让你尝尝自己犯错的苦果 ♩
♩ Choking on the taste of your mistakes ♩
♩ 现在轮到你跪下了 ♩
♩ And now you're the one on your knees ♩
♩ 这就是你反咬喂养之手的下场 ♩
♩ That's why you bite the hand that feeds ♩
myiosus cckkcc